Place a 100×80×10 mm plate
[Box]  Arm box — click ground to place
[W]  Plate width 100 mm
[H]  Plate depth 80 mm
[D]  Plate thickness 10 mm
[Click]  Place box on ground
Select the top face
[Click]  Select face
[Look at]  Orient camera to the top face
Set hole Ø 6 mm — Inset auto-fills from Ø, thickness, material
[Hole Ø]  Hole diameter 6 mm
Inset 9.0 mm from each edge at corners
[Place hole…]  Arm — click near corner 1
[Click]  Snap near corner 1 → inset
Hole 1 of 4
[Click]  Select face
[Place hole…]  Arm — click near corner 2
[Click]  Snap near corner 2 → inset
Hole 2 of 4
[Click]  Select face
[Place hole…]  Arm — click near corner 3
[Click]  Snap near corner 3 → inset
Hole 3 of 4
[Click]  Select face
[Place hole…]  Arm — click near corner 4
[Click]  Snap near corner 4 → inset
Hole 4 of 4
Finished plate — 78831 mm³